sunnyrentals.com 2015-03-23

# Privacy Statement

  * Privacy Statement
  * General Terms of Use
  * Advertiser Terms
  * Rate Card
  * Partner Terms

We understand that conducting business and making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part and we take this trust very seriously.

This Privacy Statement describes the ways in which we will use the data you provide through the SunnyRentals.com website ("our website"), which is owned and operated by SunnyRentals.com Aps ("we" or "us"). Please note that this Privacy Statement is an integral part of our website and the services offered to you and cannot, in any way, be separated from the [General Terms of Use](http://www.sunnyrentals.com/terms/general-terms-of-use) or from the membership, usage or transaction process.

By providing information through this site and/or by establishing a Member or Property Owner account with us, you indicate your acceptance of the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

This Privacy Statement addresses:

  * What information we collect online from you
  * How we use the information
  * With whom we may share the information
  * What choices are available regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  * What types of security procedures are in place to help protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control
  * How you can correct any inaccurancies in your personally identifiable information
  * How we notify you of material changes to this Privacy Statement
  * When the Privacy Statement became effective
  * If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact SunnyRentals.com customer service by email using the [Contact Us](http://support.sunnyrentals.com/customer/portal/emails/new) form

## Member sign-up

SunnyRentals.com enables you to register an account with us to become a member. When you choose to become a SunnyRentals.com member, we will require you to provide certain information and request that you provide other information at your discretion. If you do not provide us with the required information, you will not be entitled to have an account with us and be a SunnyRentals.com member. The information we may require or request includes at least your name, email address, telephone number, postal address, a unique log-in name, password, and password validation. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including: (1) personal identification; (2) to facilitate your enquiries to property owners and other requests for other travel products and services; (3) to allow us to contact you for customer service, if necessary; (4) to customize the content of our website to meet your specific needs; and (5) to conduct research and to make product improvements to the services we offer on our website. In addition, your email address is collected to send you an email message confirming your account registration and each enquiry you submit online. To help us understand the effectiveness of our email communications, we may deploy technologies that provide confirmation when you open one of our e-mail messages. As a member, you also will occasionally receive updates from us about special offers, new SunnyRentals.com services, and other noteworthy news items. You may decline to receive these email messages. Please see the section entitled "Choice/opt out," described below.

## Member profile

In addition to the information noted above, you can choose to provide us with travel preferences, credit card billing information, and other personally identifiable information. This information is primarily used to assist members in making enquiries and reservations quickly without having to type in the same information repeatedly.

## Property Owner sign-up

SunnyRentals.com enables property owners, managers and agents to register an account with us to become a Property Owner. When you choose to become a SunnyRentals.com Property Owner, we will require you to provide certain information and request that you provide other information at your discretion. If you do not provide us with the required information, you will not be entitled to have an account with us and be a SunnyRentals.com Property Owner. The information we may require or request includes at least your name, company name, email address, telephone number, postal address, a unique log-in name, password, and password validation. This information is collected on the registration form and the Account & Settings section for several reasons including: (1) personal identification; (2) to identify you as the owner (or manager) of any of the property listings you may create and market towards the users visiting SunnyRentals.com; (3) to publicly publish your contact details on you property listings to enable potential guests to contact you; (4) to allow us to contact you for customer service, if necessary; (5) to customize the content of our website to meet your specific needs; and (6) to conduct research and to make product improvements to the services we offer on our website. In addition, your email address is collected to send you an email message confirming your account registration and to send you alerts regarding important events in your account according to your contact preferences. To help us understand the effectiveness of our email communications, we may deploy technologies that provide confirmation when you open one of our e-mail messages. As a Property Owner, you also will occasionally receive updates from us about special offers, new SunnyRentals.com services, and other noteworthy news items. You may decline to receive these email messages. Please see the section entitled "Choice/opt out," described below.

## Payments for subscriptions and services

Property Owners may choose to pay for Premium subscriptions and other services to more effectively market their property listing. During the purchasing and payment process, we ask you to provide billing and payment information required for the purchase, including billing name, address, company name, VAT number, and your credit card number and expiry date. Your billing details may be viewed and edited in the Account & Settings section.

## Booking enquiries

When you make a booking enquiry by filling out the "Enquiry form" on any property listing on our website, we ask you to provide personally identifiable information by filling out and submitting an online form (if you are not a SunnyRentals.com member already). This information includes: your name, telephone number, email address, travel dates and other information related to your proposed stay. We supply this information to the individual property owner securely within our system, who will respond to you initial request. Property Owners may respond to you by email from our system or from their own external email program. Your contact details are stored in our system and are accessible by the property owner and SunnyRentals.com staff in order to facilitate a booking, or to advise you of future booking opportunities in the same property. You may decline to receive future email messages from this Property Owner or SunnyRentals.com. Please see the section entitled "Choice/opt out," described below.

## Booking enquiries referred to external agents

Some of our property listings are managed by Property Agents, who have their own websites and online systems for you to reserve and book a property directly. In the case, that you choose to make a booking enquiry about such a property, we may redirect you to the Property Agent's website, sending with the request the details that you provided in the enquiry form. Any additional information that is requested on a third party website is not governed by this Privacy Policy; you will then be governed by the terms on that third party website.

## Surveys, campaigns and competitions

From time-to-time, we may request information from you through surveys, campaigns or competitions. Participation in these surveys, campaigns or competitions is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice as to whether or not to provide this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as postcode). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our website. Although we may use a service provider to conduct these surveys or contests, as we note in the section on "Information Sharing," these service providers may not use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose.

## Information from other sources

We may receive information about you from third-party sources and add it to your account information. This information may include: updated delivery and address information from third parties, which we use to correct our records and facilitate proper delivery of our services and communications; information about travel purchases made on websites owned by affiliated companies, which we use to better understand your travel needs; and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer tied to information about you. We use both session ID (or temporary) cookies, which terminate when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which are stored on your hard drive.

We use cookies for several reasons. For example, cookies allow you to login without having to type your login name each time, allowing you to simply provide your password to access the system. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can set your browser options to block them in the future. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website; however, your access to some areas and features of our website will be limited.

A cookie file also may be placed on your hard drive by third-party advertising companies that we contract. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about travel-related goods and services that you may be interested in. SunnyRentals.com does not have access to or control over these cookies that may be placed by tmail, by filling out ours. Those advertising networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt out of advertisement targeting. If you would like to find out more information, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The third-party advertising companies may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. This can be accomplished by them using a web beacon (a single-pixel GIF), which is placed on our website to collect anonymous information. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process is anonymous and does not link online actions to an identifiable person. If you would like more information and want to explore the option of not having this information collected by third-party advertisers, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Tags

In conjunction with our own and our affiliates' marketing campaigns, we may also use technology to capture certain information relating to reservations you make through our website. We will usually collect this information by placing a web beacon (a single-pixel GIF) within our reservation pages. The information we collect is anonymous and will include the total amount of the transaction and the system-generated booking reference. We will use this information to monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and may pass this on to our affiliates for similar purposes. We may employ a third party service provider to collate and report on the information collected.

## Log files

Like most standard website servers we use log files that collect Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number and location on a page of clicks. We use this information to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, diagnose problems with our servers, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Special offers and updates

As noted above, established SunnyRentals.com Members and Property Owners may occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals about which they may be interested. Out of respect for your privacy, we present you with the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice/Opt-out" section below.

## Trip information and customer feedback

If you book a property through the our website, we will send you an email prior to your date of travel, containing up-to-date information relevant to your trip and travel destination which you may find useful; we will on occasion include information about other products and services which may be of interest to you in connection with your forthcoming trip. We will give you the choice to opt-out of receiving these emails for future reservations. In the interests of maintaining a high standard of service for our customers, we may also send you an email once you have completed your travel, so that you can provide a rating and review for the property you booked, and provide us with valuable feedback on your travel experience, although we will offer you the choice of not receiving these types of emails in the future.

## Newsletter

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask you to provide contact information, such as name and email address. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the "Choice/Opt-out" section below.

## Service announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out service-related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these non-promotional communications, although you can deactivate your membership.

## Customer service

We communicate with you on a regular basis to provide requested services. This may include responding through email, fax or phone, in accordance with the your wishes.

## Choice/opt-out

We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used by SunnyRentals.com to send promotional communications and various alerts. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving these communications following "unsubscribe" instructions given in the emails you receive, editing the Alerts & Newsletterssettings in your profile, or by contacting our customer services.

## Legal disclaimer

Although we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may be required by law to disclose information you have provided in obtaining our travel products or services. We may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could damage or bring harm to others. In addition, it may be necessary for us to provide customer information to third parties, such as credit card companies, for the purpose of resolving disputes that arise in the normal course of business.

## Aggregate information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

## Authorised service providers

We may share your personally identifiable information with authorised service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf. For example, we use an outside a credit card processing company and bank cheque processing company to bill you for goods and services. We may also rely on service providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, perform business and sales analysis, and provide marketing assistance. These companies do not have any independent right to share, store, or use the personally identifiable information we provide for any secondary purpose. We also may contract with reputable third parties to facilitate the distribution of survey, promotion, or sweepstakes programs. Upon completion of these projects, all information is returned to us. Finally, we will occasionally share aggregated information with our service providers. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information and is used to develop featured programs and content that will be of interest to our members and our website visitors.

## Suppliers

We may provide information about your bookings either reserved or purchased on our website to the suppliers who will fulfill your travel reservation. Although we may also offer travel products from airlines, car rental agencies and other suppliers that are reputable companies, we have not placed limitations on these suppliers from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Therefore, we encourage you to review the information privacy practices of any travel suppliers whose products you purchase on our website. In addition, these travel suppliers may also contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about your confirmed reservation.

## Affiliated/referring websites

If you were referred to our website from another website, we may share personally identifiable information about you with the referring website to better understand the use of our website. Although we believe that the website companies from which you were referred to us are reputable companies, we have not placed limitations on the referring websites companies from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Therefore, we encourage you to review the information privacy practices of any website that referred you to our website.

## Affiliated companies

We may share some of your personally identifiable information with affiliated companies around the world that are committed to providing you with a comprehensive array of travel packages and services to meet your travel needs. Sharing this information allows us to better understand the ways in which our various product and service offerings can assist travelers. To the extent that these affiliated companies have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other customers.

## Business transfers

As we continue to look for ways to better serve our customers, we may sell subsidiaries or business units. We also may be acquired by or merged with another company. In such instances, customer information may be one of the transferred business assets.

## International transfers

We will handle your personally identifiable information in the European Union. In addition, the third parties with whom we may share your information, as described above, may be established in countries outside the European Union, such as in the United States. By using our website you understand and agree that your information will be held and used in the European Union and other countries where our partners, service providers and affiliated companies may be established.

## Links

Please be aware that our website contains links that lead to other sites. These sites may collect personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information collection practices or policies of such websites.

## Information security

We take steps to help protect the personally identifiable information you provide to us. For example, we use leading encryption technology to encrypt credit card numbers. We also restrict access to personally identifiable information to those employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative). In addition, the servers that store personally identifiable information are contained in a locked facility. If you have any questions about the security of your information, please send an email to Customer Care.

## Accessing personally identifiable information

You can request access to, and update, the personally identifiable information we have collected about you. In order to exercise this right, you can e-mail our Customer Support at Customer Care or contact us by post at the contact information listed below. You can also can change your personally identifiable information on the Account & Settings page of our website.

## Privacy Statement changes

If we change our privacy practices, we will modify this Privacy Statement, and its effective date, accordingly so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use it, and to whom we may disclose it. We also will notify you of any material change to this Privacy Statement by placing a prominent notice on our website. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

## Contact information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Statement, please contact us by email, by filling out our [contact form](http://support.sunnyrentals.com/customer/portal/emails/new).

Postal Address:  
SunnyRentals.com Aps  
Danish company nr. 32552897  
Frederiksborggade 5A 1. sal.  
1360 Copenhagen K  
Denmark
